STEFAN STEFANOVIC

JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Ivana Gorana Kovacica, 38/9 Nis, 18000 Serbia

PHONE

+381 60 344 0402

EMAIL

sstefandev@gmail.com

SKILLS

HTML5/CSS3

SCSS/BOOTSTRAP

JavaScript

React/Redux/Gatsby

NPM/Webpack

Version Control (GIT)

NODE.js/Express

MongoDB/PostgreSQL

JWT/OAuth

Websockets/Restful API

Python

LANGUAGES

English

....

Serbian

....

PROFILE

Before talking about qualifications and professional abilities, I would like to introduce myself. Taking web development as a profession not only fulfills my pocket but also my heart because it has been my passion since my early teenage.

I'm an open-minded web developer who's ready for new challenges. I have spent most of my career in web development.

I am currently working on becoming a JavaScript full-stack developer.

I believe that people should do things which they are good at or in which their hearts lays. That's why I chose web development as my career because I believe I'm good at this and I am always honest and I am never afraid of doing hard work.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Cashier, NIS Gazprom Neft

Sep 2018 - Jun 2019

Frontend Developer, Upwork

Feb 2020 - Jan 2021

- · Developed and maintained static websites.
- · Made design decisions for the client.
- Developed scalable applications and responsive websites.
- Worked closely with program staff to ensure grant objectives were met.

EDUCATION

High school degree, High School "9.maj"

Oct 2013 - May 2017

INTERNSHIPS

Frontend Developer Intern, FAE Games

Feb 2021 — May 2021

- · Working with Wordpress and React (with create-wp-theme npm package).
- · Creating Shop and Database with Woocomerce plugin rest API.
- · Working closely with the designer.
- · Rendering and sorting data from Wordpress API and custom plugins.

Nis

Nis

Nis

Nis